const engPitanjaLvl3 = [
    {
        question: "Put the letters in the correct place to get the correct name of the plant",
        letters: "A M L O C H E M I",
        correctAnswer: "chamomile",
    },
    {
        question: "Put the letters in the correct place to get the correct name of the plant",
        letters: "D L R N A E V E",
        correctAnswer: "lavender",
    },
    {
        question: "Put the letters in the correct place to get the correct name of the plant",
        letters: "T I M N",
        correctAnswer: "mint",
    },
    {
        question: "Put the letters in the correct place to get the correct name of the plant",
        letters: "A P S E R Y B R R",
        correctAnswer: "raspberry",
    },
    {
        question: "Put the letters in the correct place to get the correct name of the plant",
        letters: "R I C H B",
        correctAnswer: "birch",
    },
    {
        question: "Put the letters in the correct place to get the correct name of the plant",
        letters: "K O A",
        correctAnswer: "oak",
    },
    {
        question: "Put the letters in the correct place to get the correct name of the plant",
        letters: "C E B E H",
        correctAnswer: "beech",
    },
    {
        question: "Put the letters in the correct place to get the correct name of the plant",
        letters: "G O K I N G",
        correctAnswer: "ginkgo",
    },
    {
        question: "Put the letters in the correct place to get the correct name of the plant",
        letters: "E L E T T N",
        correctAnswer: "nettle",
    },
    {
        question: "Put the letters in the correct place to get the correct name of the plant",
        letters: "N I P E",
        correctAnswer: "pine",
    },
    {
        question: "Put the letters in the correct place to get the correct name of the plant",
        letters: "G I F",
        correctAnswer: "fig",
    },
    {
        question: "Put the letters in the correct place to get the correct name of the plant",
        letters: "V I Y",
        correctAnswer: "ivy",
    },
    {
        question: "Put the letters in the correct place to get the correct name of the plant",
        letters: "S L E N D I N",
        correctAnswer: "lindens",
    },
    {
        question: "Put the letters in the correct place to get the correct name of the plant",
        letters: "M E N L O",
        correctAnswer: "lemon",
    }
];

export default engPitanjaLvl3